<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Medicare.gov Blog</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.medicare.gov/blog/zfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 14:42:11 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 14:42:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>This spring, put prevention into practice</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The start of spring is a reminder of new beginnings – the longer hours of daylight, sprouting tulips and warmer weather are all indicators of a new season, and a new reason to be proactive with your health. One simple way to manage your health is to practice preventive care. Preventive services can find health problems early, when treatment works best, so taking advantage of them is a crucial step in maintaining a healthy lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have Medicare, then you have access to a variety of preventive tests and screenings, most at no cost to you. If you’re new to Medicare, we cover a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/preventive-visit-and-yearly-wellness-exams.html&quot;&gt;“Welcome to Medicare”&lt;/a&gt; preventive visit during your first 12 months of Part B coverage. This visit includes a review of your medical and social history related to your health and education and counseling about preventive services, including certain screenings, shots, and referrals for other care, if needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’ve had Part B for longer than 12 months, you can get a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/preventive-visit-and-yearly-wellness-exams.html&quot;&gt;yearly wellness visit&lt;/a&gt; to develop or update a personalized prevention plan based on your current health and risk factors. In addition to these important wellness visits, Medicare covers screening tests for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/diabetes-screenings.html&quot;&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/colorectal-cancer-screenings.html&quot;&gt;colon cancer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/mammograms.html&quot;&gt;breast cancer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/bone-density.html&quot;&gt;osteoporosis&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/cardiovascular-disease-screenings.html&quot;&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/obesity-screening-and-counseling.html&quot;&gt;obesity management&lt;/a&gt;, just to name a few. Check out our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/preventive-and-screening-services.html&quot;&gt;complete list of Medicare-covered preventive services&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So as you tend to your garden this spring, make a commitment to tend to yourself too. Practice &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/preventive-and-screening-services.html&quot;&gt;preventive care&lt;/a&gt; so you can you stay healthy, live longer, and delay or prevent many diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:35 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/03/01/prevention.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/03/01/prevention.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 ways to become an informed Medicare consumer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Each day, you make important choices about your finances, health, privacy, and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During &lt;a href=&quot;https://owa.hhs.gov/owa/redir.aspx?C=ihr8C-E7tE2JkjQSqHaKgss_odF_F9IId0-TfEMT3J6gu_K9rgRcvuBqbuT0VVBo5vjYV2NHoMI.&amp;amp;URL=http%3a%2f%2fwww.ncpw.gov%2f&quot;&gt;National Consumer Protection Week&lt;/a&gt; (NCPW), the first week of March, non-profit organizations and government agencies focus on helping you take advantage of your rights and make better-informed choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medicare has 5 things you can do to help you become an informed Medicare consumer:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.     Know your rights. As a person with Medicare, you have certain &lt;a href=&quot;https://owa.hhs.gov/owa/redir.aspx?C=ihr8C-E7tE2JkjQSqHaKgss_odF_F9IId0-TfEMT3J6gu_K9rgRcvuBqbuT0VVBo5vjYV2NHoMI.&amp;amp;URL=http%3a%2f%2fwww.medicare.gov%2fclaims-and-appeals%2fmedicare-rights%2feveryone%2frights-for-everyone.html&quot;&gt;rights and protections&lt;/a&gt; designed to help protect you and make sure you get the health care services the law says you can get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.     Protect your identity. Identity theft happens when someone uses your personal information without your consent to commit fraud or other crimes. Keep the following personal information safe:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your Social Security Number (SSN)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your Medicare number (or your membership card if you’re in a Medicare Advantage or other Medicare health plan)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your credit card and bank account numbers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get more information on how to &lt;a href=&quot;https://owa.hhs.gov/owa/redir.aspx?C=ihr8C-E7tE2JkjQSqHaKgss_odF_F9IId0-TfEMT3J6gu_K9rgRcvuBqbuT0VVBo5vjYV2NHoMI.&amp;amp;URL=http%3a%2f%2fwww.stopmedicarefraud.gov%2fpreventfraud%2findex.html&quot;&gt;protect yourself from identity theft.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.     Help fight Medicare fraud. Medicare fraud takes money from the Medicare program each year, which means higher health care costs for you. Learn how to &lt;a href=&quot;https://owa.hhs.gov/owa/redir.aspx?C=ihr8C-E7tE2JkjQSqHaKgss_odF_F9IId0-TfEMT3J6gu_K9rgRcvuBqbuT0VVBo5vjYV2NHoMI.&amp;amp;URL=http%3a%2f%2fwww.medicare.gov%2fforms-help-and-resources%2freport-fraud-and-abuse%2freport-fraud%2freporting-fraud.html&quot;&gt;report fraud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.     Get involved with other seniors with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://owa.hhs.gov/owa/redir.aspx?C=ihr8C-E7tE2JkjQSqHaKgss_odF_F9IId0-TfEMT3J6gu_K9rgRcvuBqbuT0VVBo5vjYV2NHoMI.&amp;amp;URL=http%3a%2f%2fwww.smpresource.org%2f&quot;&gt;Senior Medicare Patrol &lt;/a&gt;(SMP). The SMP educates and empowers people with Medicare to take an active role in detecting and preventing health care fraud and abuse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.     Make informed Medicare choices. Each year during the fall Open Enrollment Period (October 15–December 7), review your plan to make sure it’s going to meet your needs for the following year. If you’re not satisfied with your current plan, you can switch during the Open Enrollment Period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://owa.hhs.gov/owa/redir.aspx?C=ihr8C-E7tE2JkjQSqHaKgss_odF_F9IId0-TfEMT3J6gu_K9rgRcvuBqbuT0VVBo5vjYV2NHoMI.&amp;amp;URL=http%3a%2f%2fwww.ncpw.gov%2f&quot;&gt;NCPW&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about the campaign, see which agencies and organizations are able to help you, and to find out if there are any NCPW activities happening in your area.&lt;br /&gt;
Also, check out our videos for tips on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fY9lmEKlu88&quot;&gt;preventing Medicare fraud&lt;/a&gt; and see how seniors are learning to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z1_mGVPkOdE&quot;&gt;stop, spot, and report fraud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:33 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/03/01/consumer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/03/01/consumer.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medicare helps you with better nutrition</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The saying may go “an apple a day keeps the doctor away,” but that’s not the whole truth. While apples are healthy and delicious, there are many other important factors in having a nutritious diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;69% of U.S. adults are considered overweight or obese. An unhealthy body weight puts you at a greater risk for many diseases like type 2 diabetes, heart disease, and some types of cancer. However, a healthy diet and exercise can help you lower these risks and better your overall health. Not sure how to get started? Medicare can help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medicare covers 15-minute face-to-face individual behavioral therapy sessions and 30-minute face-to-face group behavioral counseling sessions to help you lose weight if you have a body mass index (BMI) of 30 or more. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/obesity-screening-and-counseling.html&quot;&gt;Find out if you qualify for this service.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://recipes.millionhearts.hhs.gov/&quot;&gt;Million Hearts® Healthy Eating &amp;amp; Lifestyle Resource Center&lt;/a&gt; can be a good resource in getting or maintaining a healthy diet. Million Hearts is a national initiative to prevent 1 million heart attacks and strokes by 2017. The resource center was developed in partnership with &lt;em&gt;EatingWell &lt;/em&gt;magazine and features calorie-controlled, heart-healthy recipes for you and your family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Planning and understanding your diet can help you stay on track. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.supertracker.usda.gov/&quot;&gt;SuperTracker&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.choosemyplate.gov/&quot;&gt;ChooseMyPlate.gov&lt;/a&gt; can help you plan, analyze, and track your diet and physical activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start off National Nutrition Month right by having a nutritious diet and becoming a healthier you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:17 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/03/01/nutrition.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/03/01/nutrition.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Saving Dollars Makes Sense, with Medicare</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With rising prices on essentials like groceries, you’re not alone if you’re keeping a close eye on your wallet. Many Americans are facing financial challenges today, and health care costs are no exception. Luckily, there are many ways you can save money on your health care costs if you have Medicare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have limited income and resources, you may qualify for Medicaid – a joint federal and state program that helps with Medical costs. Even if you don’t qualify for Medicaid, there are other programs that may help you pay for your Medicare premiums and other costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 4 Medicare Savings Programs are: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/your-medicare-costs/help-paying-costs/medicare-savings-program/medicare-savings-programs.html#qmb&quot;&gt;Qualified Medicare Beneficiary (QMB) Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/your-medicare-costs/help-paying-costs/medicare-savings-program/medicare-savings-programs.html#slmb&quot;&gt;Specified Low-Income Medicare Beneficiary (SLMB) Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/your-medicare-costs/help-paying-costs/medicare-savings-program/medicare-savings-programs.html#qi&quot;&gt;Qualifying Individual (QI) Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/your-medicare-costs/help-paying-costs/medicare-savings-program/medicare-savings-programs.html#qdwi&quot;&gt;Qualified Disabled and Working Individuals (QDWI) Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you qualify for Medicaid or a Medicare Savings Program, you’ll also get Extra Help paying for your prescription drugs automatically. If you don’t automatically qualify Extra Help, you can apply online at SSA.gov.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s important to call or fill out an application if you think you could qualify for savings—even if your income or resources are higher than the amounts listed on Medicare.gov. These amounts change yearly, and there may be another savings program you are eligible for depending on your specific situation. To find out if you are eligible for savings through one of these programs, call your &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/Contacts/Default.aspx&quot;&gt;State Medicaid Program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 00:00:51 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/02/22/savings.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/02/22/savings.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This Valentine’s Day, give yourself the gift of a healthy heart</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Although popular love songs might tell you otherwise, a broken heart can’t kill you – but &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cdc.gov/heartdisease/&quot;&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt; can. Heart disease is the leading cause of death in the United States, taking 600,000 lives each year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might not be able to avoid Cupid’s arrow, but you can take steps to lower your risks and prevent heart disease. Start by scheduling an appointment with your doctor to discuss whether you’re at risk for heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medicare will cover a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/cardiovascular-disease-screenings.html&quot;&gt;cardiovascular screening&lt;/a&gt; at no cost to you every 5 years. The screening includes tests to help detect heart disease early and measures cholesterol, blood fat (lipids), and triglyceride levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you and your doctor discover that you’re at risk for a heart attack or stroke, there are steps you can take to help prevent these conditions. You might be able to make lifestyle changes (like changing your diet and increasing your activity level or exercising more often) to lower your cholesterol and stay healthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;February is American Heart month, so start it off right by visiting the &lt;a href=&quot;http://recipes.millionhearts.hhs.gov/&quot;&gt;Million Hearts® Healthy Eating &amp;amp; Lifestyle Resource Center&lt;/a&gt;. Million Hearts is a national initiative to prevent 1 million heart attacks and strokes by 2017. The resource center was developed in partnership with &lt;em&gt;EatingWell &lt;/em&gt;magazine. It features lower sodium, heart-healthy recipes and family-friendly meal plans to help manage sodium intake, a major contributor to high blood pressure and heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hjMfwA4ToVE&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; for more information about the Million Hearts initiative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:57 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/02/01/heart-2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/02/01/heart-2.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Choosing a dialysis facility just got easier</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you the kind of shopper who reads reviews or looks at ratings before you make a purchase? Wouldn’t it be helpful to have the same kind of ratings when choosing a dialysis facility?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can be overwhelming when you’re faced with having to choose a health care provider. Providers and facilities differ in the safety and quality of care they give, and having quality ratings available to compare providers can help you make more informed health care decisions. That’s why we’ve made it easier to use the information on our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/dialysisfacilitycompare/#search&quot;&gt;Dialysis Facility Compare&lt;/a&gt; (DFC) site by adding star ratings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compare websites are the official source for information about the quality of health care providers, and star ratings are just one of many ways we’re working to make quality information easier to understand and compare. These ratings are based on an established and respected process for developing standards. The DFC rating gives a 1 to 5-star rating based on information about the quality of care and services that a dialysis facility provides. Right now, we do this based on 9 quality measures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The DFC ratings are just one example of how we’re commited to helping you make informed health care decisions. Our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/nursinghomecompare/search.html&quot;&gt;Nursing Home Compare&lt;/a&gt; site already uses star ratings to help consumers compare nursing homes and choose one based on quality. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/physiciancompare/search.html&quot;&gt;Physician Compare&lt;/a&gt; has just started to include star ratings in certain situations for physician group practices. We’re planning on adding star ratings to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/hospitalcompare/search.html&quot;&gt;Hospital Compare&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/homehealthcompare/search.html&quot;&gt;Home Health Compare&lt;/a&gt; later this year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 11:58:50 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/01/22/dfc.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/01/22/dfc.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protect yourself – get screened for cervical cancer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know all women are at risk for cervical cancer, and it occurs most often in women over 30? Fortunately, Medicare covers 2 types of screening test – the Pap smear and human papilloma virus (HPV) test – that can help find cancer and other health problems early and improve recovery and survival rates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;January is Cervical Health Awareness Month. Watch our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EBtnj3N3IMs&quot;&gt;Cervical Health Awareness Month video&lt;/a&gt; and visit our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/cervical-vaginal-cancer-screenings.html&quot;&gt;cervical &amp;amp; vaginal cancer screenings&lt;/a&gt; page to learn what these tests do and how often they’re covered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, visit the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nccc-online.org/&quot;&gt;National Cervical Cancer Coalition&lt;/a&gt; website to find ways you can raise awareness about cervical cancer and how you can make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 00:00:26 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/01/21/cervical-2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/01/21/cervical-2.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you at high risk for glaucoma?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have diabetes or a family history of glaucoma? Are you African American and 50 or older, or are you Hispanic American and 65 or older? If so, your risk of getting glaucoma may be higher, but don’t worry – Medicare covers a glaucoma test once every 12 months for people at high risk for glaucoma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;January is National Glaucoma Awareness Month. Find out more about Medicare’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/glaucoma-tests.html&quot;&gt;glaucoma screening coverage&lt;/a&gt;. Also, visit the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.preventblindness.org/&quot;&gt;Prevent Blindness&lt;/a&gt; website to see how you can join the ongoing fight against vision loss.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:00:37 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/01/20/glaucoma.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2015/01/20/glaucoma.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get your Medicare ready for 2015</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you make resolutions for the new year? Here are some easy ones you can keep that will help get you ready for 2015:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Check to see that you have the right insurance card to use when you go to the doctor in 2015.&lt;/strong&gt; Did you change your health or drug plan during Medicare Open Enrollment? If you did and you haven’t received your new card or welcome packet by January 1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt;, contact your plan for help. If you need to fill a prescription right away, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/part-d/coverage/filling-prescription-without-card/fill-prescriptions-without-card.html&quot;&gt;find out how to fill a prescription without your card&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you changed from a Medicare Advantage Plan (like an HMO or PPO) back to Original Medicare, use your red, white, and blue Medicare card when you go to the doctor. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.socialsecurity.gov/medicarecard/&quot;&gt;Get a new card if you lost or damaged yours, or need to update your information&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Budget for next year’s Medicare Part B deductible.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, if you have Medicare Part B and you’re in Original Medicare, you’ll have to meet your deductible before your Medicare coverage pays for services and supplies. Next year, the Medicare Part B deductible will be $147, the same as it was in 2014. Plan your health care budget to account for the increased cost of doctor visits for the time that it will take to cover your deductible. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/your-medicare-costs/costs-at-a-glance/costs-at-glance.html&quot;&gt;Find out more about Medicare costs in 2015.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.  Schedule appointments to get any preventive tests or screenings.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medicare covers all sorts of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/preventive-and-screening-services.html&quot;&gt;preventive services&lt;/a&gt; to keep you healthy and screenings to check for health problems, and many are covered each year at no cost to you. Ask your doctor when you should schedule your &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/coverage/preventive-visit-and-yearly-wellness-exams.html&quot;&gt;wellness visit&lt;/a&gt; and other screenings. You can also use &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mymedicare.gov/&quot;&gt;MyMedicare.gov&lt;/a&gt; to track your visits and make a calendar of preventive services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk to your doctor about these covered preventive services to find out what’s right for your health needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;Make sure your drug or health plan meet your needs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If not, Medicare has a way for you to get the coverage you want instead of having to wait for the next Open Enrollment. At any time during the year, you can switch to a Medicare Advantage Plan or Medicare Prescription Drug Plan that has a 5-star rating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plan ratings are based on member surveys, information from doctors and health care providers, and other sources. The plan ratings are scores that show the quality and performance of the plan, on a scale of 1 to 5 stars, with 5 being the highest rated plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can make this change once per calendar year. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medicare.gov/find-a-plan/questions/home.aspx&quot;&gt;Find 5-star health and drug plans in your area&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to check &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicare.gov/&quot;&gt;www.medicare.gov&lt;/a&gt; for the latest Medicare news and information, and have a happy and healthy new year!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 00:00:43 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2014/12/08/get-ready.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/2014/12/08/get-ready.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medicare Open Enrollment: is Medicare still on your “to do” list?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“To do” lists are very helpful during this hectic time of year. If something important isn’t written down, it’s easy to forget. If you still haven’t crossed off “Compare Medicare coverage” from your to do list, time is running out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medicare Open Enrollment ends this week on December 7. To help you sort through your choices, try using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://medicare.gov/find-a-plan/questions/home.aspx&quot;&gt;Medicare Plan Finder&lt;/a&gt;. You can review the plan options in your area and decide the best mix of benefits and costs that meets your needs and budget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In these last few days of Medicare Open Enrollment, take a moment to review your health care coverage and see if you need to make any changes for next year. If you decide you’re happy with the plan you have now, and the plan’s still being offered next year, you don’t need to do anything. But if you’re thinking about making any changes, now’s the time to act so you can cross another item off your to do list.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:01:08 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.medicare.gov/blog/open%20enrollment/2014/12/01/medicare-open-enrollment-is-medicare-still-on-your-to-do-list.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.medicare.gov/blog/open%20enrollment/2014/12/01/medicare-open-enrollment-is-medicare-still-on-your-to-do-list.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>open enrollment</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
